Traders are turning a few hundred into
hundreds in thousands in profits with
tokens that are available for anyone to
buy giving literal 1,000 x's on their
money and this isn't a rare occurrence
under the current market conditions we
are seeing tokens run to tens in
millions in market cap on a daily basis
in the last couple weeks alone we've
seen goat guinon fcoin loose peanut and
moodang all run two multi hundred
million market caps and those aren't the
only ones there's plenty of tokens that
go to 1 million 5 million 10 million
which are great opportunities so today
is the first in a multi-part series
where we discuss meme coins how to find
them where to trade them how to identify
those 100x tokens and everything you
need to know to best equip yourself for
this memec coin super cycle ladies and
gentlemen welcome back to another crypto
Gorilla video as usual I not a financial
adviser hit that subscribe button and
let's dive right into the video so meme
coins have been around for quite some
time you've most likely heard of tokens
like Doge which was the main meme coin
of the 2021 cycle going as far as being
featured on Saturday Night Live with
Elon Musk but the world of meme coins
has dramatically changed with the
creation of pump fun which is the first
topic of this video series now pump fun
is a platform where anybody can launch a
token within 15 seconds essentially for
free and it's really as simple as giving
a token a name uploading an image
pressing create coin and then boom your
token is available for anybody to buy
now if I just leave the pump fund Page
open here for a minute you'll see that
there are literally dozens of tokens
being created every single minute and
thousands of tokens being created every
single day and these are the tokens that
the average memec coin Trader is buying
just staring at their monitors scanning
every single coin and trying to multiply
their money now I know what your first
thought probably is seeing all these
tokens being created anybody can create
a token in 15 seconds there's no value
behind any of this stuff so why would
anyone in their right mind buy this and
the answer is quite simple gambling
people don't come to crypto because they
love the technology or because Society
is crumbling they come to crypto because
they want to 1,000 extra money and quit
their job so that's the first Trope you
need to get over when you're looking at
this stuff probably thinking it's stupid
and worthless a ton of people thought
nfts were stupid during the 2021 nft
cycle but I know plenty of people who
made millions of dollars Trading nfts so
it doesn't matter if something is stupid
all that matters is can you make money
from it so yes this is gambling but
people love to gamble I put this kind of
trading between sports betting and slot
machines in sports betting your
knowledge of the sport and your
understanding of a certain team or
player Dynamics can give you an edge and
allow you to place better bets similarly
your understanding of crypto Twitter
following the main characters tracking
the right wallets and understanding the
general culture of what's happening can
also give you an edge but I also say
it's like slot machines cuz a lot of
this stuff is hit or miss it is very
much just gambling and we're going to
look at some of the stats here shortly
you might very well be better off
gambling cuz literally anything can
happen with these tokens they can go to
zero in an instant so now you hopefully
have a better understanding of why
people are buying these tokens so let's
take a look at how the platform works so
whenever a token is launched if it gets
enough money that flows through it it's
going to go through three different
stages so stage one is the stage that a
majority of pump fund tokens never leave
and this is where they're trading on a
bonding curve which is a mathematical
concept between the price and supply of
an asset look it doesn't matter you
don't need to understand what a bonding
curve is all you need to know is that
the token needs to have enough buys to
reach a
$69,000 market cap in order for it to go
to stage two which is the migration
stage now during the migration stage the
token is not tradable so if you bought
it you won't be able to sell it for a
short period of time and if you want to
buy it you're going to have to wait till
it reaches stage three the graduation
stage where the token is now live on
radium in other words it becomes a real
token but becoming a real token is not a
guaranteed recipe for success in fact a
ton of tokens that graduate either go
straight down or they have a very short
life cycle now looking at some of the
data you can see that there have been
almost 3 million tokens that have been
deployed through pump fund and
especially during the month of October
you can see here there's anywhere from
20,000 to 30,000 tokens being launched
every single day however if we look at
the number of tokens that are actually
graduating to radium you can see for the
20 to 30,000 tokens that are being
launched every single day only three to
maybe 500 on the top end are actually
reaching stage three the graduation
stage and if we look at the total number
that have graduated since the beginning
only
42,000 tokens total and that's of 3
million so roughly a 1.4% chance that a
token goes from stage one all the way to
stage three and just to show you how
many people are doing this the platform
to date assuming they haven't sold a
single salana that they've earned
because they earned their fee in salana
they have made
$175 million in fees and they take a 1%
fee up until the token reaches radium
and that's not to say there's not a ton
of competitors that have come out since
the launch of pump fun in fact whenever
there's a brand new chain upcoming ones
like abstract bar chain monad people are
always looking for what's the pump fun
of that chain but despite all the
competitors and despite the fact that
pump fun is only available on salana it
is still very much the king now yes 175
million or whatever number they've
actually made is a ton of money but like
I said they only make a fee up until the
token reaches the graduation phase until
it reaches radium which probably
explains why they just launched the
advanced version of their platform for
trading which is a great segue into our
next section where are people trading
these tokens because personally I don't
know anybody who uses the advanced
version of pump fun instead most people
I know are using tools like bullx or
photo on which these tools are really
going to help you visualize the three
stages now I will have detailed
tutorials for each of these tools in the
near future I will also put my referral
links in the description down below so
make sure you use those if you're going
to be trading on either of these
platforms but for the sake of this
tutorial I'm just going to pick bullex
you can use either one you want they
both have advantages disadvantages and
they operate relatively the same but if
you're on bulock you're going to want to
go to you what's going to be called pump
Vision I have Neo Vision just because
it's a new version of the platform
that's not available yet to the public
but you're going to click pump Vision
here or if you're on photon you are
going to click on Meme scope so here you
can see the three stages that I spoke
about earlier we have the brand new
tokens which is the stage that only 1.4%
of tokens actually manage to escape we
have tokens that are about to graduate
and you can see here we have two tokens
that are currently migrating so if I
click this one I can't currently buy it
because it's in the the process of
migrating and if I stare at this page
long enough you're going to see it jump
from the second column to the third
column which is the final stage the
graduated stage where it has reached
radium so this is the casino this is
where a majority of the Traders I know
are spending their day staring at their
screen clicking every single token with
their friends in a voice chat
researching them and trying to find
which ones are going to 10 50 100x now
not everybody does that some people
actually just trade within this section
buying tokens that are at 5 6 7,000
market cap and selling it when it
reaches 20 30,000 whatever it is they
don't care if it makes it to the
graduation stage because they've already
2 3 4X their money they dump the coin
and they just move on to the next one
they don't care what happens to it
especially that only 1.4% of tokens
actually graduate now the other funny
thing about this page you'll probably
have noticed that a lot of the tokens
right now are Trump related and that's
because we have the elections that are
happening at the time of me filming this
video a lot of people actually get their
news from pump fun I remember when the
Trump assassination attempt happened I
have some friends who weren't on Twitter
they weren't watching the news but they
knew something happened around an
assassination and Trump because all the
tokens that were coming out were related
to that topic which is one of the ways
to make money with this platform however
I'm going to cover that in a future
video now I understand I'm probably
making this sound quite easy to do you
just buy a token at 5,000 you sell it at
40,000 boom you 8 extra money but it is
very hard to make money here in fact the
stats that I've seen over the summer
were only 3% of Traders actually make
$1,000 or more meaning a majority of
people probably over 90% of people
actually lose money trading here so your
odds of making money especially when you
start are quite low I would only do this
with money you are 100% willing to lose
and especially when you're starting off
I would view it as my cost of tuition
your education cost just assume you're
going to lose money so don't throw in
$5,000 into this platform I would start
very small even with like 0.01 salana
per trade and don't care about making
you know 50x 100x or $100,000 you should
only be trying to learn because like I
said if you start this now you're going
to have the edge when retail actually
comes in so that's it for today's video
I hope you found it educational if you
did be sure to give it a like as that
really helps my channel reach a wider
audience I'm going to be doing a ton of
these videos doing tutorials going into
details on how to find the 100x tokens
that's probably going to be my next
video on Wednesday and I'm also going to
be interviewing some of the best meme
coin Traders out there so if you haven't
already done so would you kindly hit
that subscribe button hit that
notification Bell so you can find out as
soon as I drop a video thank you for
watching the crypto
gorilla peace
[Music]